George Beck Papers
George Beck Papers
- Box 11814
  - Lincoln Bank
    - Check desk (Box 11814)
    - Money and file cart (Box 11814)
    - Stairway details (Box 11814)
    - Misc. Equipment stand (Box 11814)
    - General (Box 11814)
  - Systems analysis brochure ibm (Box 11814)
  - Mr. and Mrs. G. Nait (Box 11814)
  - Mental hygiene center (Box 11814)
  - Harry Ward Liquors (Box 11814)
  - Correspondence and various design plans (Box 11814)
  - Elfun Society, 1962-1964 (Box 11814)
  - Management conference, Grossinger's, 1960 (Box 11814)
- Box 11815
  - Published materials (Box 11815)
  - Bulletins (Box 11815)
  - Booklets (Box 11815)
  - Brochures (Box 11815)
  - Fairmont fair (Box 11815)
  - News clippings
    - McKinley death, 1901 (Box 11815)
    - Roosevelt death, 1945 (Box 11815)
    - World War II ends, 1945 (Box 11815)
    - Association Island and G.E. Syracuse (Box 11815)
  - Advertisements (Box 11815)
- Box 11816
  - Slides (Box 11816)
- Box 11817
  - Portfolio (Box 11817)
- Box 11818
  - Portfolio, including modern water colors by G. Beck (Box 11818)
- Box 11819
  - Portfolio, including various drawings (Box 11819)